<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rey Ylagan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rey Ylagan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello Python &amp; R</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/07/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/07/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>library(reticulate) Today we will be learning the reticulate packedge in R and how to use Python in the same R Markdown file!
Variable Assignment #This is a R Code Chunk R_Var &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;Hello I was made in R&amp;quot; Here is a variable assignment in R
#This is a Python Code Chunk Py_Var = &amp;quot;Heyo I was made in Python&amp;quot; Here is variable assignment in Python
 Acessing Different Variables #Python Code Chunk print(r.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Intro The data used in this project was collected from the USDA’s Atlas of Rural and Small-Town America. Located at: https://www.ers.usda.gov/data-products/atlas-of-rural-and-small-town-america/
These datasets were interesting to me as they contained data for the entire nation, but each observation was a small local. So this dataset gives a good representation of the country by area, population was not accounted for in this project, and had unique county classifications and employment measurments that sparked my curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction With the ongoing pandemic I absorb statistics about the state of the virus, and to verify this information I went to HealthData.gov and found their Community Profile Report (CPR) – County-Level. The following is some information on the dataset based on its documentation. It was developed by Data Strategy and Execution Workgroup in the Joint Coordination Cell, under the White House COVID-19 Team. Each observation in the dataset is county-level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
